<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>David Wolfe</title><subtitle>A space for creative and professional endeavors. Capture The Flag (CTF) WriteUps, HackTheBox WriteUps, Cyber Security blog posts. Learning all the time.</subtitle> <updated>2024-08-17T00:18:47-05:00</updated> <author> <name>David Wolfe</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2024 David Wolfe </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>Animated Background</title><link href="/posts/BackgroundBlender/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Animated Background" /><published>2024-08-08T09:00:00-05:00</published> <updated>2024-08-08T09:00:00-05:00</updated> <id>/posts/BackgroundBlender/</id> <content src="/posts/BackgroundBlender/" /> <author> <name>David Wolfe</name> </author> <category term="3D Art" /> <category term="Blender" /> <summary> Description This is probably the project I’m most proud of to date. I’m planning on adding more deatils to this post about the techniques I used to create this, but it was a lot of geometry and shader nodes. I learned so much about the different inputs and ways to manipulate objects through geometry nodes. The end goal of this project was to have a looping, vaporwave wallpaper to use with wal... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Friend Character Model</title><link href="/posts/FriendBlend/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Friend Character Model" /><published>2024-07-14T09:00:00-05:00</published> <updated>2024-07-14T09:00:00-05:00</updated> <id>/posts/FriendBlend/</id> <content src="/posts/FriendBlend/" /> <author> <name>David Wolfe</name> </author> <category term="3D Art" /> <category term="Blender" /> <summary> Overview: This was a bit of a speed sculpt competition. My friend and I decided to see who could recreat the other in blender faster. This was done over an 2 or 3 hours on a random weeknight. I’m happy with the results and vibes this one gives off. It was also refreshing to do a cartoon character where I didn’t have to worry about super accurate sculpting or details. Results </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Low Poly Cat</title><link href="/posts/ToadBlend/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Low Poly Cat" /><published>2024-07-12T09:00:00-05:00</published> <updated>2024-07-12T09:00:00-05:00</updated> <id>/posts/ToadBlend/</id> <content src="/posts/ToadBlend/" /> <author> <name>David Wolfe</name> </author> <category term="3D Art" /> <category term="Blender" /> <summary> Description This one was a lot of fun for me personally. I’m not sure anybody would look at these results and say they are good, but I can look at them and enjoy how silly they are. This was a great project to practice low poly sculpting, manual UV unwrapping, and some light rigging as a bonus! Now please, enjoy these silly renders of my digital cat (yes, he’s polydactyl). Results </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Carl Fredricksen</title><link href="/posts/CarlFredricksen/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Carl Fredricksen" /><published>2024-05-27T09:00:00-05:00</published> <updated>2024-05-27T09:00:00-05:00</updated> <id>/posts/CarlFredricksen/</id> <content src="/posts/CarlFredricksen/" /> <author> <name>David Wolfe</name> </author> <category term="3D Art" /> <category term="Blender" /> <summary> Description This was a weird one for sure. I’m not sure there is much to say about this, other than I learned a ton about sculpting and texutre paiting. It was a unique challenge for me to have to paint digital makeup on a poorly sculpted fast late at night. My friend was very happy with the results Results </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Coffee Bar</title><link href="/posts/CoffeBar/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Coffee Bar" /><published>2024-05-21T09:00:00-05:00</published> <updated>2024-05-21T09:00:00-05:00</updated> <id>/posts/CoffeBar/</id> <content src="/posts/CoffeBar/" /> <author> <name>David Wolfe</name> </author> <category term="3D Art" /> <category term="Blender" /> <summary> Description I was running low on inspiration when I decided to remake the most import part of my living space, my coffee bar! Biggest takeaway from this project was the utility of the boolean modifier when adding round objects to flat toplogy. This can be seen in the steam knob on the side of the espresso machine in the final render. Results </summary> </entry> </feed>
